So hello friend welcome to my YouTube channel so
how are you all then today's video is going to be
very knowledgeable for all of you Suman whenever
we purchase an insurance policy for our car then the
biggest confusion
and difficulty we face is which
company's car insurance should we purchase
because there are many insurance companies in the market you get many
offline policies,
many online policies are available,
in some you get some discount, in some you get some
advance,
if I talk about it then in which company
you get to see some different payments and
in which company you get to see very limited advance, so in such a situation there is a
lot of
confusion as to which company
's policy we should purchase so
friends in today's video I have
brought its solution for all of you, in this
video I am going to tell you about some such top 10 car
insurance companies
whose insurance you should get done, along with that
we will verify everything, in the
company which I am going to tell you in this video
how many network garages it has,
miss network garages in a way  Whenever
you purchase an insurance policy, if
you have a claim, then how many network garages are there
in the area of ​​​​mins, how many garages are available in Over India or Pan India,
where your insurance
claim will be settled, along with which advanced services are you
getting,
what benefits are you going to get and about the
prices, I am going to talk in this video,
so friends,
if you watch this video till further, then you are going to get very good
knowledge and information through this video,
so keep watching the video till further, I
am your friend, your host Aman, without
wasting time, let's start today's video, the
insurance which comes at number one in the morning
is from HDFC, this is going to be a very good
insurance for all of you,
if I talk about network garages, then there are 8200
plus network garages and the rating is also
given 4.5 stars, the highest, if I
talk about the benefits, then
you also get overnight car repair
under the insurance under the services, sir,
you also get fast claim settlement  You get
24/7 road assistance and Pan
India is available at your home today.
If you want to clean anything, then you will get
easy and quick claim settlement. The
second number one is Bajaj. This is also a
well-known brand and it provides you with a very good
insurance policy.
Its rating is 4.5 stars,
but the network garage is 4500 plus.
If we talk about HDFC
EGO, then its network is a little less than that.
You get to see it here.
In benefits, you get zero depression.
You get 24/7 claim settlement from here.
You also get the option of PaySU Drive
here and its
settlement is also going to be very good.
After this, the third number one is
called Lens, Reliance General. If you want, you
can do third party and first party also. It has a
4.5 star rating and if we
talk about network, then it
comes at the highest rating.
Its network garage is 8500 plus. Pan
India  You will find its service stations available
here, you can get your claim video
settled, it is fully digital,
you get a paperless process here
and whatever your clean settlement is, it also becomes
digital and you get a
clean settlement very easily,
you also get a lot of advance,
after this the next insurance is of Tata
Tokio, if you want you can get comprehensive or
third party,
along with this you also get zero depression tax
here and 4000-300 plus here
you get network garages,
its rating is 4.5 stars, if I talk about network garages then
you get fewer network garages here, but
you also get a lot of additional features in this policy
like you get no charge road
resistance, 50% discount, the
best one in NC is
Tata AIG's comprehensive or
third party insurance, this is also a very
well regarded insurance and you can get it too,
its rating is 4.5 stars,
network garages are also very good
You get 7500 plus homes today, along with
significant discounts
on premiums, and 12% advances for
personal accidental injuries.
Claim settlement is also very
easy and quick. Next
is SBI General's private car
insurance, or you can get both third-party and first-
party insurance. It has a 4.0 star
rating and a 6-star, 400-plus
screen network.
You can easily get treatment at hospitals.
Its claim settlement process is also
very fast; it's going to be a digital
process. You also get
more than 12% advances for claims.
After this, perhaps
digital car insurance, which has a
4-star rating and 5800-plus
network garages, also offers on-
card damage insurance. There's a
PayI enabled process here, and
you also get the option to PaySU Drive. The claim
settlement process is
completely digital, with a pickup and drop
facility.  Repairs are also being offered here,
which is a very good thing.
After this, there is your ICC
Lombard, which you can get from either third party or
first party.
Its rating is 4.0 stars and its network is 4800 plus. It has a
digital process
and its claim settlement process is
also going to be paperless and digital. The
next insurance that
comes is D New India Insurance Motor
Package, which you can get from both third party and first party.
Its rating is 3.5 stars
and its network garages are a little less. If
seen, you will get 500-600 plus network
customers. So
you get these services.
You get a very good claim settlement. You
also get personal accidental tax.
Further, and a very good settlement is done on its
claim settlement. After this, the last one comes to which
you
can get a lot of discount on premium,
which is very good. If
you want, you can get
both third party and first party
insurance on this.  You can have a 3.5 star rating
and if I talk about network garages, then
it is not shown yet, it is
not displayed, but there are many
network garages available pan India, so
you will not face any problem in claim settlement, the
process is quite easy, along with this you get
this enabled self-infection and
clean settlement is also done very quickly,
as you have seen, these are some of the top ten
insurance companies,
you can consider both car insurance and bike insurance,
it is included in the top ten companies,
along with this I have also told you the rating of each insurance policy
or insurance company, this
overall
rating is given on many parameters like it is on
customer reviews, it is on
network garages
and the claim settlement rates, after
looking at all these things a particular rating is given,
now from all these insurance policies
and insurance companies, I have told you that this is the
best and is included in the top 10,
you can choose any of them  You
can purchase the policy of the insurance company, whether it is your two
wheeler or four wheeler insurance,
you can purchase first party insurance or
you can also purchase third party insurance,
I have made this video for both the conditions and if
you have any doubt related to this video
or if you have any doubt related to insurance, then
you can ask in the comment section of this video, I will reply to you as soon as possible
in the next video, till then goodbye
[Music]